本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： Nick冰 猫 Dennings Cinderella
校对： cinderella   后期： 泡面小小
东区女巫前情回顾...
Previously on Witches of East End...
- 那个 我叫温迪 - 利奥
- I'm Wendy, by the way. - Leo.
我叫利奥 有样东西你肯定感兴趣
My name's Leo. I got something you're gonna love.
等一下 你是准备不告而别?
Wait. You were just gonna go without saying good-bye?
- 我觉得你在等我 - 没有啊
- I feel like you're waiting for me. - I'm not waiting.
我爱你 阿奇博尔德
I love you, Archibald.
我知道你和阿奇博尔德的事 他才不关心你
I know about you and Archibald. He doesn't care about you.
- 他在利用你 - 为什么你要撒这种谎?
- He's using you. - Why are you lying like this?
你也许能骗得了她 阿奇博尔德
You may have fooled her, Archibald,
但是我知道你想干嘛
but I know exactly what you're up to.
- 金造螺球! - 不!
- Pila metalli! - No!
我要把你千刀万剐!
I'll kill you as many times as it takes!
- 我很抱歉 - 你杀了我爸爸
- I'm sorry. - You killed my father.
你和你的家人对我意义重大
You and your family mean so much to me.
我已经为你计划好了
I have big plans for you.
天哪 等等
Oh, my God. Wait.
英格丽德...
Ingrid...
怎么说我都是你姨妈
I'm still your aunt.
你还是我侄女
You're still my niece.
你不该这样子
This isn't who you are.
事实上...
Actually...
我觉得这才是真正的我
I think this is exactly who I am.
不
No.
夺命掏心!
Acidum adere!
东区女巫 第一季第07集
我还以为你回家了呢
Oh, I thought you went home.
我会让你一个人整理仓库么
Like I'd let you finish inventory by yourself.
你对我的评价可不怎么样 对吧?
You do not think much of me, do you?
我拒绝回答
I am not gonna answer that.
- 里面真热 - 是啊 罗杰一直不修火炉
- It is hot in here. - I know. Roger refuses to fix the furnace.
我一直在和他纠结这个呢
I keep bugging him about it.
要我去和他说说吗?
Want me to bug him?
人家说我很擅长烦人的
I've been told I am very good at bugging people.
我也能作证
I can vouch for that.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
对不起
Sorry.
有时候我会忘记
Sometimes I forget.
你... 会忘记什么?
You... forget what?
基利安...
Killian...
弗雷娅? 弗雷娅?
Freya? Freya?
什么事? 怎么了? 发生了什么?
What? What? What's going on?
你吵醒我了 你像条鱼似的翻来覆去
Oh, you woke me up. You're flopping around like a fish.
我肯定是做恶梦了
Oh. I must have been having a bad dream.
是啊 你一直在说梦话
Well, you were talking a lot.
我说了什么?
What was I saying?
我不知道 很难理解 但是...
I don't know, I could barely understand, but...
肯定是在呻吟
There was definitely some moaning.
其实 听起来还蛮性感的
Actually, it sounded kind of sexy.
额 不好意思 我一直这样
Oh, I'm sorry. I've always done this.
我小的时候 英格丽德曾经在大半夜
When I was a kid, Ingrid used to bang on the wall
捶着墙壁叫我闭嘴
in the middle of the night and tell me to shut up.
好吧 我... 清楚地记得你说梦话
Well, I am... well aware of your sleep talk.
你第一次说爱我 就是在你睡着的时候
Oh, the first time you said you loved me, it was in your sleep.
- 你从没和我说过呢 - 我不想你尴尬
- You never told me that. - I didn't want to embarrass you.
你知道我从不为任何事尴尬的
You know I don't get embarrassed about anything.
好吧 也许是我有点尴尬
Okay, maybe I was embarrassed.
我... 我...
I... I... '
因为虽然我不知道这算不算数
Cause even though I didn't know if it counted,
但是我也说我爱你了
I said it back.
算数
It counted.
你梦到了什么?
What were you dreaming about?
我不知道 不记得了
I don't know. I don't remember.
一点都不记得了?
Nothing at all?
我一向不记梦的
I just don't remember my dreams.
也许下次我该靠近点听
Maybe I should listen a little closer next time,
看看我能不能自己听出来
see if I can figure it out for myself.
我要去上班了
I gotta get to work.
哇 怎么了?
Whoa. What's going on?
你知道我会说梦话的吧?
You know how I have that whole sleep-talking thing?
- 是啊 - 我昨天晚上把达什吵醒了
- Yeah. - Well, I woke Dash up last night,
我正在做着跟基利安有关的梦
and I was in the middle of a dream with Killian.
他听到你说基利安的名字了?
And he heard you say Killian's name?
感谢上帝 没有
No, thank God,
不过这样下去他早晚会听到
but it's only a matter of time before he does.
最糟糕的是 我醒着的时候根本
And the worst part is, I don't even think about Killian
就没想过基利安 但是睡着了就会梦到他
when I'm awake, but sleep Freya hasn't gotten the memo.
- 不太好啊 - 是啊
- Oh, that is not good. - No.
我最不希望达什通过我的梦话
The last thing I need is Dash figuring out what happened
知道我和基利安之间的事
between me and Killian because I scream it out in my sleep.
你和基利安之间有什么事?
What happened between you and Killian?
- 我们接吻了 - 什么?!
- We kissed. - What?!
你说过你有感觉有欲望
You said you had feelings and desires,
可这事儿是什么时候发生的?
but when?
- 在我的订婚典礼上 - 弗雷娅...!
- Um, at my engagement party. - Oh, Freya...!
我一做就知道错了 我当场逃走了
I knew it was a mistake the second I did it; I ran out instantly.
想不到你竟然没告诉我 你什么都告诉我的
I can't believe you didn't tell me this. You tell me everything.
我不想你批判我
I didn't want you to judge me.
- 你真的觉得我会批判你? - 是啊
- You really think I would judge you? - Yeah.
好吧 也许以前会
Fine. Maybe, once upon a time,
但是在我经历了那么多事情以后
but after all that I've been through,
我再也没有资格批判任何人
I am in no position to judge anyone ever again,
特别是你
especially not you
不过是一念之差 我做的事更过分
for a momentary slip. I've done worse.
我猜你不打算告诉达什喽?
And I assume telling Dash the truth is not an option?
没门 他永远不会发现的
No way. He can't ever, ever find out.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay. So,
这本书里有一个关于控制梦的部分
there is an entire section on dream control in this book
有一个咒语
where you can come up with a spell.
我们只需要一束头发
And we are just going to need a bunch of hair,
- 好的 - 一些生姜和茴香种子
- Okay. - Some ginger and some anise seeds.
基利安的头发?
Killian’s hair?
呼! 都置办好了
Whew! That's taken care of.
- 你好 英格丽德 - 你好
- Hey, Ingrid. - Hey.
- 她怎么了? - 我不知道
- What is wrong with her? - I don't know.
她清除掉那面墙了?
Did she get rid of the wall?
是的 我和你妈妈早上溜进了费尔黑文的墓地
Yes. Your mother and I snuck into the catacombs at Fair Haven
消除了枝毒的痕迹
and managed to erase all traces of ramus mortium early this morning.
控制梦? 这是个大咒语
Dream control? It's a big spell.
都准备好了?
Everything okay?
不 不 没呢 还没
No, no, it's not. Not really.
好吧 告诉姨妈你需要什么
Okay, tell your aunt Wendy how she can help.
你能解读我的卡片吗?
Can you read my cards?
塔罗牌和显灵板不一样 弗雷娅
Tarot is not like Ouija, Freya.
你不能只是问问题
You can't just ask it questions.
它只显示它想显示的东西
It reveals what it wants to reveal.
还有 我不喜欢为家人占卜
Besides, I don't like reading for family.
帮帮忙 求你了
Oh, come on, please?
我们可以在明天图书馆活动结束以后做
We could do it after that library event tomorrow.
- 你去吗? - 是啊 当然
- You are going? - Yeah. Of course.
是啊 为什么不去呢?
Yeah. What?
有钱人 免费食物 开放式酒吧...
Rich men, free food, open bar...
我会早点到的... 相当早
I'll be there early... ish.
告诉我
Tell me something,
要是我告诉你我的内心有黑暗面
if I told you there was a darkness inside of me,
你会怎么说?
what would you say?
英格丽德 你是我见过的最正统
Ingrid, you are the most proper,
最守规矩的人
rule-abiding person I know.
我是说 你从图书馆拿本书回家都要正规登记
I mean, you won't even take a library book home without officially checking it out.
才不是呢 好吧 是这样的...
That is not true. Okay, fine, it is...
但是有句话说你不能凭封面来评价书的
But there's a reason they say you can't judge a book by its cover.
等等 我们指的是真正的书吗?
Wait, are we still talking about actual books?
你好
Hi.
你好 欢迎来到东区图书馆
Hi. Welcome to the East End library.
我能帮你什么吗?
How can I help you?
能帮我找到尽可能多的这类书
Can you find as many of these books as possible
然后放到我桌子上来吗?
and bring them to my table?
- 当然 可能会花点时间 - 尽量快点
- Uh, sure. It may take a few minutes. - Just make it sooner rather than later.
喂
Hey.
你不能像是对待你的仆人一样对别人
You can't just treat people like your servants.
你要是想要那些书 自己去找吧
If you want these books, you can find them yourself.
我还以为图书管理员会很乐于助人的
I thought librarians were supposed to be helpful.
是的 不过要看那个人配不配
We are, when people deserve it.
- 好吧 我明白了 - 你明白什么了?
- Oh. I get it. - You get what?
你 我打赌你以前是纠察队长 是吧?
You. I'll bet you were a hall monitor, weren't you?
你当了图书管理员是因为你就会唬人...
And you became a librarian because you just live to shush peop...
听着 伙计 你一点都不了解我
Listen, buddy, you don't know anything about me.
- 我很了解 - 真的吗?
- I know enough. - Oh, really?
你以为在图书馆大声喧哗
Because you're the kind of guy who thinks
就是造反分子就是破坏规矩
yelling in the library makes you a rebel
其实只会显得你自以为是
and a rule breaker when it really just makes you a smug,
缺乏体谅 傲慢无礼...
inconsiderate, disrespectful...
我们到这里来吧
And we are moving over here.
也许你比我想象的要黑暗一点呢
Maybe you're a little darker than I thought.
嘿 你要为你妈妈去参加图书馆活动吗?
Hey, are you going to this library thing for your mom?
你好啊
Hello to you, too.
我当然要去 你觉得我有的选?
Of course I'm going; You think I have a choice?
怎么了? 你在看什么?
What? What are you looking at?
你的头发...
Your hair...
你已经下班了
Do you actually mean for it to look like that
你不是特意把头发弄成这样的吧?
when you leave for the day?
什么?
Excuse me?
我是说 你头发这么乱
I'm saying, this whole messy thing,
不是故意弄的 是吧?
it can't really be a plan, right?
我当然没有故意弄头发
Of course I don't have a plan for my hair.
我不知道你什么意思
I don't even know what that means.
好吧 我觉得你要剪个头
Well, I think you could use a haircut,
而且我肯定佩内洛普会乐意的
and I'm pretty sure Penelope would appreciate it.
我真的没空
Well, I really don't have time.
事实上你有空 因为你运气不错
Actually, you do, because luckily,
我对剪头发很拿手
I am very talented at cutting hair.
在高中的时候我经常帮我朋友剪
I used to do all my friends' hair in high school.
这是我众多天赋之一
It's one of my many gifts.
- 但我不想剪啊 - 我才不管
- But I don't want a haircut. - I don't care.
走
Let's go.
好嘞
Okay.
别太短了 好吗?
Not too short, okay?
放松 一点都不会痛的
Relax. It's not gonna hurt at all.
嘿 别动
Hey. Stay still.
天哪 这里就像是在蒸桑拿
Man, it's like a sauna in here.
我知道 我一直在叫罗杰修炉子
I know. I keep asking Roger to fix the furnace.
要我去说一下吗? 大家都说我很会烦人的
Want me to bug him for you? I hear I'm very good at bugging people.
- 你说什么? - 我很会烦人
- What did you say? - I'm good at bugging people.
怎么啦?
What?
没事
Nothing.
你还好吧?
You okay?
我很好啊 怎么啦?
Yeah, I'm fine. Why?
你似乎在担心什么事
You seem worried about something.
你有心事的时候就是那个表情
You do that thing with your face when you're worried.
我没什么表情啊
I don't do a thing with my face.
你现在就是那个表情
You're doing it right now.
我在你后面... 你看不到我的表情
I'm behind you... You can't see my face.
但是我感觉的到 这是我的天赋...
But I can sense it. It's one of my gifts...
我很了解你
I can read you like a book.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
过来
Come here.
各位
Hey, guys.
艾米 你好 我来把这儿收拾干净
Amy. Hi. Let me just help clean up in here.
别 别 不用 我来吧 等会我出去找你们
No, no, no, I got it. I'll just see you out there.
消亡之梦的碎片
Delens somnium meum hominis.
希望这个能有用
Oh, I hope this works.
你还好吗?
You okay?
我想你现在一定感到很困惑
I bet you must be feeling awfully confused right now.
我加入了邪教
I was in a cult.
就要跟阿奇博尔德・布朗宁结婚的时候
I was about to marry Archibald Browning.
温迪杀了我
Wendy killed me.
我记得所有这些事 仿佛是昨天发生的
And I remember all of this like it was yesterday.
- 我感到的不仅仅是困惑 - 什么意思?
- Confused doesn't even begin to cover it. - What do you mean?
我知道弗雷娅和我总是年纪轻轻就去世了
I know that Freya and I always die young.
- 你怎么会这么想? - 妈妈!
- Oh, where do you come up with this? - Mom, please!
我看了所有的照片
I can see all of these pictures,
但是我们从没有变老过 从没有
but we are never old, ever.
所以我的看法是 我们总是在这个年纪死去
So my theory is, it's because we always die around now.
- 好吧 - 天呐
- Okay. - Oh, my God.
- 是的 你说的对 - 我不敢相信
- Yeah, you're right. - I can't believe this.
- 但是... - 但是什么
- But... - But what?
这次的情况完全不同
This life is completely different.
你们从没有活得这么长过
You guys have never lived this long before,
我可以保证你们的安全
and I have kept you safe.
这是我的责任 而且
That's my job, and
你不需要担心这些 因为你的任务
you don't need to worry, because your job
就是尽情地享受生活...
is to live your life to the fullest...
醒来
Wake up.
母亲...
Mother...
我不是你母亲 你认识我 我是雅典娜
I'm not your mother. You knew me as Athena.
欢迎回来 英格丽德 我好想你
Welcome back, Ingrid. I missed you.
英格丽德躲着我 弗雷娅要我读她的牌
Ingrid is avoiding me, and Freya asked me to read her cards.
那就去呀
Ugh! So do it.
- 但是我不能说给她听 - 那就别去了
- Well, I can't just read them to her. - Don't do it.
我也不知道该怎么办 温迪
I don't know anymore, Wendy.
如果结果显示她英年早逝了呢?
What if it reveals she dies young?
你不想她这样知道这件事 不是吗?
You don't want her to find out that way, do you?
是的 但是她也许会通过其他方式知道
No, but she might figure it out anyhow.
- 嗯 你说的对 - 她有预言的天赋
- Yeah, I guess you're right. - With her gift of premonition.
英格丽德知道了 她有点生气
Ingrid found out. She's mad.
所以她才这么诡异吗?!
Oh. Is that why she's acting so weird?!
当然了 还有其他事
Yeah, among other things.
她也知道了那次是你杀死了她
She also found out about the time you killed her.
什么?
What?
我给你这个是让你来浇水的 是吧?
I gave you that so that you could help water, right?
浇水
Aspergo.
她是怎么知道的?
How did she find out?
你认为呢? 她编了一个咒语
How do you think? She cooked up a spell.
关于早逝的事你是怎么跟她说的?
What did you tell her about the whole dying-young thing?
我本想告诉她待在屋里
I wanted to tell her to stay in her room,
关上窗户 让我保护她
shut the blinds, let me keep her safe,
但是却告诉她要活在当下
but instead I told her that she should seize the moment while she can.
当你不知道自己还剩多少时间的时候
When you don't know how much time you have left,
就要抓住现在的每分每秒 不是吗?
you want to make the most of every second, right?
是啊
Yeah.
- 我还活着吗? - 不算是
- Am I alive? - Not quite.
这下好了 现在...
There. Now...
这至少可以保持一两天
That should hold, at least for a day or two.
我为什么在这儿?
Why am I here?
你的姨妈温迪偷了
Your aunt Wendy stole something
我父亲阿奇博尔德的东西 也就是你的爱人
from my father Archibald, the man you loved,
你愿意誓死保护的人
and the man you died trying to protect.
- 我要把它拿回来 - 什么东西?
- And I need it back. - What is it?
它叫巨蛇座
It's called serpens clavem.
是一只金色的蛇
It's a golden snake.
它的尾巴看起来像一把钥匙
The tail looks like a key.
我要你把它拿回来
I need you to get it back for me.
你可以完成的
You can do this for me.
我要你设法让温迪单独跟你在一起
I want you to get Wendy alone,
说服她把东西交出来
and convince her to give it back.
作为回报 你可以杀了你姨妈
In return, you can kill your aunt,
就像多年前她杀了你一样
the one who murdered you all those years ago.
嗨 利奥
Hi, Leo.
你在这儿做什么? 你怎么知道我在这儿?
What are you doing here? How did you even find me?
我自有我的办法
I have my ways.
我最近一直在想你 很想你
Um, I've been thinking about you lately, a lot, actually.
搞笑 自从你扮成我的邻居 睡了我
That's funny, seeing as how I never heard from you again
还偷了我最自豪的蝴蝶以后
after you pretended to be my neighbor,
我好像再也没有收到过你的消息
slept with me, and then, stole my prized butterfly.
那只猫真是你的吗?
Was that even really your cat?
那只小猫绝对是我的
Oh, that little kitty is very much mine.
听着 我... 我真的想打电话跟你道歉
Listen, I... I... I really did mean to call and apologize.
你拿我的喜马拉雅皇冠蝶做了什么?
So what did you do with the Himalayan Stamped Crown you took from me?
你在易贝上把它卖了吗?
You sell it on eBay?
不 我没有卖
No, I didn't sell it.
我真的需要它
I really needed it.
而且我还不能解释原因
And... and I can't explain why.
好吧 听着
All right, look,
我很感激你营造的整个神秘的氛围
I appreciate the whole mysterious vibe thing.
我也肯定有人喜欢这种感觉
I'm sure it works on some guys.
只是我现在不想浪费时间去琢磨清楚
I just don't have the time to figure you out right now.
好吗? 我很忙
Okay? I'm busy.
等等 等等 等等 对不起
Okay, wait, wait, wait. Sorry. Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你说的很对 我的确... 的确对你撒谎了
What you said was right. I did... I did lie to you.
的确... 利用了你 我心里很愧疚
I did... use you, and I feel terrible about it.
你也许不想琢磨我 但是我想琢磨你
You may not want to figure me out, but I want to figure you out.
我们第一次见面的时候 有一种感觉
When we first met, there was this connection.
我们之间有火花
A spark between us.
而且我想继续发展下去
And I want to get to the bottom of it.
真的吗?
You do?
我姐姐今天对我说了一些很有意义的话
My sister said something to me today that made a lot of sense.
抓住机会享受生活
You got to grab life while you can.
谁知道我们还有几条命... 我的意思是
Who knows how many lives... I mean, years...
还能活几年?
We all have left?
听着 我不是外面那种玩玩而已的人
Look, I'm not in the market for someone who plays games.
我知道 我知道 我真的知道
I get it. I get it, I do.
再给我一次机会吧?
Just give me another chance?
一起去吃午餐吧
Let's go to lunch.
我发誓 我不是玩玩而已
There will be no games, I swear.
除非你想玩点什么
I mean, unless you want to play them.
你真是... 太慷慨了 亲爱的
Oh. Oh, you're... Mmm... So generous, darling.
多谢你能来 爱你
Oh, thank you so much for coming. Love you.
我很快就回来 你好
I'll be right back. Oh, hello.
英格丽德? 你在这儿呀
Ingrid? Here you are.
你好 乔治
Hey, George.
你好吗?
How are you?
很好 你今天能来真是太好了
Good. It was nice of you to come today.
当然了
Oh, of course.
我在以我的方式支持图书馆的工作
I try to support the library in any way I can.
当然了 也在... 支持你
And, uh... Support you, obviously.
多谢
I appreciate that.
- 你好啊 - 你好
- Hey, you. - Hey.
- 开心吗? - 你开玩笑吧?
- You having a good time? - Are you kidding me?
这是我在图书馆过得最开心的一次
This is the most fun I've ever had in a library.
是吗?
Is it?
我有一个让我们更开心的想法
Well, I know a way we can have even more fun.
真的吗?
Oh, really?
我们去伦敦吧
Let's go to London.
什么? 就这样吗?
What? Just like that?
你就这样掰掰手指头 我们就要去伦敦了吗?
You're just gonna snap your fingers, and we're gonna go to London?
是的 明天怎么样?
Yup. How about tomorrow?
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
我被邀请两天后在英国的医学会议上做演讲
I got invited to speak at a medical conference in England in two days.
听着 我知道这有点急 你会去吗?
Look, I know it's last minute but, are you in?
当然去了
Yes, of course I am.
有时候你可能得一个人待着...
You might be on your own for some of it, be...
我是说 我估计...
I mean, I assume you just...
你不愿意一整天听我讲
You know, you don't want to watch me speak
第三世界接种疫苗什么的
about third world vaccinations all day.
无意冒犯 我想我能找到事做
No offense, I think I can fill my time.
不敢相信我就要在我的护照上盖一个章了
I can't believe I'm gonna finally have a stamp on my passport.
盖两个吧 对 我们盖两个吧
Let's make it two. Yeah, let's make it two.
我们去英法海峡隧道看看 顺便在巴黎待几天
Let's hop on the Chunnel, we'll tack on a couple of days in Paris.
去吃一下牛角面包 喝点红酒
We'll eat croissants, drink wine.
这就是我们蜜月的预演
It'll be a rehearsal for our honeymoon.
你太让我高兴了! 太棒了！太棒了！
You are killing me! Yes! Yes!
真是不可思议
That sounds incredible.
你知道我们要像第一次约会那样
You do you realize we were supposed to be having lunch,
去吃午餐的吧?
like a real first date, right?
我刚刚有了胃口
I'm just building up an appetite.
我想是的
I think we did that.
你想去哪儿呢?
Where do you want to go?
你说吧
You choose.
我怎样都行
I'm good with anything.
你当然是啦
Yes, you are.
这项链你是在哪儿弄的?
Where did you get this necklace?
看起来很古老 很酷
Looks antique. It's cool.
我不知道
Oh. I don't know.
已经很久了 都不记得了
I've had it for so long, I can't even remember.
穿好衣服我们出发吧
Go get dressed so we can go.
好的
Okay.
总之 我一会再过来
Anyway, I should probably be getting back.
改天我们能一起去喝一杯吗?
Hey, why don't we go and get a drink some time?
好贴心 但是我现在还不想这样
That is sweet, but I'm not really in place for that right now.
怎么了? 娱乐一下你也害怕吗?
What's the problem? Are you afraid of a little fun?
- 不 我不想要这样的娱乐 - 是吗?
- No. This isn't my idea of fun. - Oh, yeah?
为何不... 告诉我你的想法呢?
Why don't you... Tell me some of your ideas?
好吧 我们就聊到这里吧
Okay. This conversation is over.
我可不这么想
I don't think that it is.
骨折
Fractura.
你弄断了我的手指 怎么...?
You broke my fingers. What...?
也许你现在该离开了
You should probably move along now.
你不必这么做的 我可以自己照顾自己
You didn't have to do that. I can take care of myself.
你和弗雷娅之间有什么吗?
Is there something happening between you and Freya?
你在说些什么啊?
What are you talking about?
我不知道 我以为...
I don't know, I thought...
感觉我刚才好像打扰到你们了
Just felt like I was interrupting something earlier.
剪头发而已
A haircut.
我知道这不关我的事
Look, I know it's none of my business,
但是 我想你们之前也许...
but, um, I just wondered if you two had maybe ever...
没有 艾米...
No. God, no. Amy...
我只是想确定我没有成为第三者...
I just want to make sure I'm not getting in the middle of something...
显然 我不是 我想去喝一杯 好吗?
Which, apparently, I'm not. I'm gonna go get a drink, okay?
- 你想要什么吗? - 不用了 谢谢
- Do you want anything? - No thanks. I'm good.
打扰一下 我们需要谈谈
Excuse me, we need to talk.
从小时候开始我就能预感到不好的事情
Ever since I was a little kid, I know when something bad
我有这种天赋
is gonna happen. I get this feeling in my stomach.
我现在就有这种感觉 莫名的
And I have the feeling, right now, out of nowhere.
你太多疑了 没什么不好的事情会发生
You're being paranoid. Nothing bad is going to happen.
我告诉你 我的骨头都能感觉到
I am telling you, I can feel it in my bones.
我以为是你的胃感觉到了呢
I thought you felt it in your stomach?
我两个地方都感觉到了
I feel it in both places.
- 如果是跟我们有关... - 哇哦!
- Look, if this is about us, um... - Whoa!
停 没有我们 从来没有
Whoa, there is no us, and there never has been.
- 这不完全正确吧 - 没什么要发生
- That's not exactly true. - Nothing is happening.
有发生过 但是是很久以前了
Something happened, but it was a long time ago.
而且只是一个吻
It was just a kiss.
我们都知道这是一个巨大的错误
And we both know that it was a huge mistake.
所以 我们不会告诉任何人
And that is why, we are never, ever, going to tell anyone,
因为这已经结束了
because it's over.
好吧 放轻松 深呼吸
Okay, relax, take a deep breath.
我保证 都会好的
It'll all be fine, I promise.
好的
Okay.
来了!
I got it!
- 英格丽德！ - 温迪姨妈 你得跟我来
- Ingrid! - Aunt Wendy, you have to come with me.
天呐 我怎么把图书馆的事情给忘了呢?
Oh, no. I forgot the library event, didn't I?
弗雷娅一定会很生气
Freya's going to be so pissed.
不 是妈妈... 她受伤了
No, no. It's mom... she's hurt.
很紧急 你得跟我来
It's an emergency. You have to come with me now.
什么? 等一下 让我...
What? Wait, let me just...
就是现在!
No! Now!
利奥 我姐姐出事了！
Leo, there's an emergency with my sister!
温迪?
Wendy?
发生了什么?
What happened?
这个变形人想用黑魔法杀死她
This shape-shifter tried to kill her with some dark magic.
- 她伤得多严重? - 很严重
- How bad is she hurt? - Pretty bad.
唯一能帮她的是
The only way to help her is
你从阿奇博尔德那里拿来的蛇钥匙
with the snake key you took from Archibald.
蛇钥匙? 我从来没提起过啊
Snake key? I never said anything about a snake key.
- 你说起过 - 不 要是说过我会记得的
- Yes, you did. - No. I would remember that.
我想母亲可能提起过
I think mother may have mentioned it.
- 是金色的... - 母亲?
- It was gold... - Mother?
等一下 你怎么知道我在这里?
Wait a minute. How did you know I was here?
你们没人认识利奥啊
Nobody knows about Leo.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是你的侄女
I'm your niece.
你从扶手上推下去 害死的那个人
The one you threw over a railing and killed.
现在你知道什么感觉了
And now you know how it feels.
醒来
Expergiscendum.
你动不了
You cannot move.
这圈不允许你动
The circle will not let you.
你总是说 我是我们中最强大的
You always said I was the most powerful one of us all.
你是变形人吗?
Are you the shifter?
变形人让我苏醒了
The shifter reanimated me.
我是英格丽德 你的侄女
I'm Ingrid, your niece.
你杀死的那个 记得吗?
The one you killed, remember?
你想从我这里得到什么?
What the hell do you want from me?
我要巨蛇座
I want the serpens clavem.
我不知道怎么跟你说
Look, I don't know what to tell you.
它早在几百年前就被销毁了
It was destroyed hundreds of years ago.
灼烧!
Ustulo!
这复仇我等了一百多年了
I've been waiting over 100 years for this revenge.
加强灼烧!
Ustulo rivulus!
是你啊
It's you.
迈克 我是迈克
Mike. It's Mike.
我能坐这张长椅吗?
Am I allowed to sit on this bench?
我要道歉
I completely need to apologize
我昨天在图书馆朝你大吼
for yelling at you, um, at the library yesterday.
没关系 我知道我可能有点...
Not a problem. I know I can be a little...
我想说谢谢帮我处理那个家伙
I wanted to say thank you for helping me with that guy.
只是想让你知道 我能自己处理
Just as long as you know, I could've handled that myself.
我知道 你看起来很能干
I have no doubt. You seem very capable.
我发现他跟踪你去了过道
But when I saw him follow you down the aisle,
就决定看着你 以防万一
I decided to check on you just in case.
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道我的名字 我能知道你的吗?
So, you know my name. Do I get to know yours?
不好意思 我是英格丽德 英格丽德・波尚
I'm so sorry. I'm-I'm Ingrid. Ingrid Beauchamp.
- 很好听的名字 - 谢谢
- Oh, that's a really pretty name. - Thank you.
很高兴认识你 英格丽德・波尚
Nice to meet you, Ingrid Beauchamp.
我应该...
I should... Oh.
妈妈
Hi, mom.
我一会就到
Yeah. I'll be right there.
我得走了 我们会在图书馆见面的对吧?
I have to run, but, um, I'll see you at the library, right?
- 我还能进去吗? - 当然 随时啊
- I'm... I'm still allowed? - Yes. Anytime you want.
好的
All right.
你见到达什了吗? 他刚刚在图书馆消失了
Hey, have you seen Dash? He just disappeared from the library.
没有 也许他去医院了呢
Not lately. He probably got paged to the hospital or something.
你知道他多爱拯救生命的
You know how much he loves saving lives.
我不这么觉得
Yeah, I don't think so.
你来了 - 怎么了 大哥?
Oh, there you are. - What's up, brother?
我一直给你打电话
I've been calling you...
怎么了?
What? What?
达什 等一下!
Dash, wait!
现在不是时候 弗雷娅
No, not now, Freya.
天呐...
Oh, my...
- 你好 有何贵干? - 我找温迪
- Hey. Can I help you? - I'm looking for Wendy.
她之前在我家 但是她忘了拿她的包
She was at my place earlier, but she left her bag, and said
好像她姐姐有麻烦了?
something about her sister being in trouble?
- 不好意思 你是谁? - 我是利奥
- I'm sorry. Who are you? - Oh... right. I'm Leo.
我是乔安娜 温迪的姐姐 我很好啊
I'm Joanna. I'm Wendy's sister, and, uh, I'm fine.
告诉我到底发生了什么?
Um, tell... Exactly what happened?
我当时在换衣服 有人敲门
Well, I... I was changing clothes, and someone knocked on the door.
温迪去开门了 等我出来想看看什么事
Wendy went to go answer it, and by the time I came out to see
她就已经走了
what was going on, she was gone.
你也没见到她 对吗? 你觉得她还好吗?
You haven't seen her, either, have you? You think she's okay?
我相信这一定是个误会
I'm sure it's just some big misunderstanding.
我会告诉她你来过 谢谢你告诉我
Um, I'll let her know you were here. Thanks for telling me.
该死的
Damn it.
快点 找到光吧
Come on, find the light.
出现项链吧
Show me the necklace.
- 达什 你在做什么啊? - 我要去伦敦
- Dash, what are you doing? - I'm leaving early for London.
我觉得我一个人离开比较好
I think it's better if I go alone.
我不知道你怎么想的...
Look, I... I don't know what you think you know about...
我听到你的话了 弗雷娅 在图书馆
I heard you, Freya, at the library.
听到你对他说的话了
Heard everything you said to him.
你听到我说这是一个天大的错误了吗?
Did you hear me say that it was a huge mistake?
这只是过去的事 不能意味什么的?
That it was in the past, and didn't mean anything?
拜托 你不能...
Come on, you weren't...
我不能怎么样?!
I wasn't what?!
我不该发现这些吗?
Huh? I wasn't supposed to find out?
我早就该猜到
Yeah, I could've guessed that.
达什 听着 我爱你
Wait, Dash, look, I love you. Please, just...
别这样 这只是个错...
This was a big mis...
我现在都不想看见你
I can't even look at you right now.
只要你告诉我蛇钥匙在哪里 这一切就会结束
This will end if you tell me where the snake is.
它已经没有了
It's gone.
即使我知道在哪里 我也不会告诉你
But if I knew where it was, I wouldn't tell you anyway.
你过去很堕落 现在也一样
You were corrupt then, and you're corrupt now.
好吧
Fine.
那我只能杀了你了
Then I guess I get to kill you.
动手吧
Go ahead.
我就坐在这里... 等着
And then I'll sit here... And wait.
等你复活后 我再杀了你 不管多少次
And when you come back to life, I'll kill you again, as many times as it takes.
英格丽德 等等 我们...
Ingrid, wait. We... we...
我不小心杀了你
I killed you by mistake.
我还是你姨妈
I'm still your aunt.
你还是我的侄女 这不是真正的你
You're still my niece. This isn't who you are.
实际上 我觉得这才是真正的我
Actually, I think this is exactly who I am.
不
No.
夺命掏心
Acidum adere!
英格丽德?
Ingrid?
- 不 妈妈 不要 - 你不是我女儿
- No, mom, please don't. - You're not my daughter.
看着我的眼睛 你知道我是谁
Look in my eyes; You know who I am.
我是英格丽德啊
I'm Ingrid.
我们等会再聊这个
Okay, we'll talk about this later.
我们先带你姨妈离开这里
Let's get your aunt and get her out of here.
恢复!
Reverte!
化为灰烬
Reverte ad vestrum priorem statum.
可你不杀人的啊
But you don't kill people.
你已经死了
You were already dead.
- 这么说不是假冒者干的? - 不是
- So it wasn't the shifter? - No.
是另一个很久以前的敌人
It was another enemy from a long time ago,
我猜 是假冒者派来的
I assume, sent by the shifter.
- 谁 什么敌人? - 你不知道
- Who, what enemy? - No one you'd know about.
我已经疗好了她的烧伤 她会好起来的
I've healed her burns, so she's going to be okay.
现在我们只能等
All we can do now is wait.
达什要一个人去伦敦
Dash is going to London without me,
我甚至不知道他还想不想娶我
and I don't even know if he still wants to marry me.
- 亲爱的 怎么了? - 他发现了
- Sweetie, what happened? - He found out.
我就知道会这样的
I knew it was gonna happen.
我只是... 自从我发现自己的身份以来
I just... ever since I found out what I am,
我的直觉变得越来越强烈
my intuition just keeps getting
而且我 我需要更加信任自己
stronger and stronger, and I, I need to trust myself more.
- 很抱歉 弗雷娅 - 达什发现什么了?
- I'm so sorry, Freya. - Dash found out about what?
我和基利安的事 我们接吻了
About Killian and me. We kissed.
- 就在她的订婚宴会上 - 那是个错误!
- At her engagement party. - It was a mistake!
那是我这辈子最大的错误
The biggest mistake of my entire life.
- 因为我就是个坏人 - 你不是坏人
- Because I'm a terrible person. - You're not a terrible person.
人都免不了犯错
People make mistakes.
可不能犯这种错误 妈妈
Not like this, mom.
相信我吧 我犯的错误更多 更严重
Oh, believe me, I've done much, much worse.
我觉得达什离开是件好事
I think it's good that Dash went away.
这样他就有机会一个人想想他怎么会这么爱你
It'll give him some alone time to remember why he loves you so much.
- 你真的这么认为? - 当然
- You really think that? - Definitely.
我们为什么要看温迪姨妈睡觉呢?
Why are we watching aunt Wendy sleep?
她不是在睡觉 她死了
She's not asleep, she's dead.
天哪 又死了?
Oh, my God, again?
没事的
It's okay.
她不会死很久的
She won't be long now.
天哪
Oh, God.
这一直不见好
Oh, that never gets any better.
欢迎回来... 很高兴看见你又活过来了
Welcome back... it's nice to see you breathing again.
好的 大家都在呢 我错过了什么?
Okay, so we're all here. What did I miss?
你被杀了 然后 一个叫利奥的朋友来看你了
You got killed, um, and, a friend named Leo stopped by, looking for you.
貌似很关心的样子 貌似有点喜欢你
Seemed concerned, seemed to like you.
我猜你听了我的话 对吧?
I guess you took my advice, huh?
嗯 有点吧
Yeah, a little bit.
- 好啦 来吧 姑娘们 - 好
- All right, come on, girls. - Yeah.
我们来让温迪恢复能量
Let's let Wendy get her strength back.
- 英格丽德 - 在呢
- Ingrid. - Yeah.
- 我能跟你说句话吗? - 当然
- Can I talk to you for a second? - Of course.
那我们没事啦? 我是说 我们扯平了?
So we're okay? I mean, we're even now?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
你妈妈没告诉你吗?
Oh, your mom didn't tell you?
你杀了我 当然 我是说 1906年的你
You killed me. Oh, I mean, you know, the you from 1906.
什么?
What?
假冒者教唆你... 以前的你...
The shifter reanimated you... the old you...
然后让你来找我报仇
And sent you after me for revenge.
天哪 我...
Oh, my God, I'm...
那 以前的我现在在哪里?
So, where is old me now?
嗯 我也不知道
Uh, um, I'm not sure.
你得问问你妈妈 不过我确定她已经搞定了
You have to ask your mom about that, but I'm sure she took care of it.
- 对不起 - 没事的 不是你的错
- I'm so sorry. - No, it's okay, it wasn't you.
不 就是我 她干什么 我也有责任
Yes, it was me. I mean, whatever she did, I'm capable of.
我们是一样的
We're the same person.
不 亲爱的 不是这样的
No, honey, it doesn't work like that.
所有的生命都完全不同
Every life is completely different.
只是生命终结的时间不同罢了
Except every life ends about now.
这可未必
Not necessarily.
要是历史能暗示什么就好了
If history is any indication.
历史也可能改变的 我看见了
History can change; I've seen it.
感觉很怪
It just feels like impossible odds.
我是说 自从我发现自己是女巫以来...
I mean, ever since I discovered what I am...
我就不断收到一些坏消息
It's been an endless parade of bad news.
感觉好像我不知道自己是谁了一样
I feel like I don't know who I am anymore.
要是有什么不同的话 我更了解你了
Well, if it makes any difference, I know who you are.
你有一颗善良的心
You have such a good heart.
你是迄今为止我最喜欢的英格丽德
You're my favorite Ingrid yet.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 我爱你 宝贝儿 - 我也爱你
- I love you, sweetie. - I love you, too.
- 还以为你回家了呢 - 我来帮忙清查
- Thought you went home. - Here to help with inventory.
- 天哪 这里好热 - 罗杰不想修火炉
- Man, is it hot in here. - Roger refuses to fix the furnace.
我不停地拿这件事烦他
I keep bugging him about it.
想让我去烦他吗?
Want me to bug him?
有人说我特别擅长烦别人
I've been told I'm very good at bugging people.
你得走了
You have to go.
什么?
What?
这是个梦... 是我最后一次梦见你
This is a dream... the last dream I'll have about you.
- 再见了 - 等等 不 你不能
- I'm saying good-bye. - Wait, no, you can't.
弗雷娅 听我说
Freya, listen to me.
这一切都不是你想的那样
None of this is what you think.
再见 基利安
Bye, Killian.
嘿 你醒了
Hey, you're up.
- 嘿 - 我做了件正确的事
- Hey. - Well, I did something right.
我念的那个咒语起作用了
The spell I did worked.
我想我再也不会梦见基利安了
I think I'm finally done dreaming of Killian.
- 你在干什么? - 弗雷娅 坐下
- What are you doing? - Freya, sit down.
我曾经规定再也不给你们两个占卜了
I made a rule that I would never deal the deck for you girls.
我觉得这是自找麻烦
I think it's asking for problems,
不过我知道你很困惑
but I know you're confused
很好奇 所以我给你做了
and curious, so I did it for you.
- 它说什么? - 很复杂
- Well, what does it say? - It's complicated.
比我想象中还要复杂
It's more complicated than I realized.
它有说我和达什将来会怎样吗?
Does it say something about my future with Dash?
我们还会结婚吗?
Are we still getting married?
我不知道会发生什么事
I don't know what will happen.
未来被包在里面
There's a shroud around the future
因为你还没有做决定
because your choice isn't yet made.
什么?
What?
这就是你
This is you
你是一切的中心 被爱和家人包围
in the center of everything, surrounded by love and family.
这才是问题
This is the problem.
什么 是骗子和皇帝吗?
What, the trickster and the emperor?
他们是镜子的两面
They're mirror images, they're often
经常以兄弟存在... 一个黑暗 一个光明
depicted as brothers... One dark, one light.
这么说一个是达什一个是基利安?
So one is Dash and one is Killian?
还有 根据牌面 他们分开了你的心
Mm-hmm, and, according to the cards, they divide your heart.
那 基利安肯定是黑暗面 对吧?
Well, Killian is obviously the dark one, right?
骗子可能是任何一个
The trickster could be either.
他可能是化妆成光明的黑暗
He could be dark masquerading as light.
这就是他干的事... 他让你困惑
That's what he does... He confuses you.
这是什么意思?
What does that even mean?
根据牌面 你会爱上他们两个
According to the cards, you will love them both.
你必须要做个决定
You have a choice to make.
一个是你的灵魂伴侣 一个是你的冤家
One man is your soul mate, the other man's your destroyer.
你的选择将会决定你的命运
Whoever you choose will decide your fate.
- 终于好了 - 什么?
- Oh, finally. - What?
我一活过来就等着跟你说话
I've been wanting to talk to you since I came back to life,
可我不想当着姑娘们的面说
but I didn't want to say anything in front of the girls.
为什么?
Why?
知道吗? 我可以喝一杯
You know what? I could use a drink.
所以呢...
So...
所以 自从你第一次遇到危险
So, you know, ever since I had the first vision of you being in danger,
我们就在努力寻找假冒者和他的目的 对吗?
we've been trying to figure out who the shifter is and what they want, right?
你是说除了毁掉我们以外?
You mean aside from destroying us?
我还不知道假冒者是谁
Well, I still don't know who the shifter is,
不过我想我知道他们的目的了
but I think I know what they want,
这可不是好消息
and it's not good news.
那 他们什么目的?
So, what is it?
死去的英格丽德不停地要巨蛇座...
Dead Ingrid kept asking for the serpens clavem...
那条金蛇
The golden snake.
- 真的吗...? - 对
- Really...? - Yeah.
那她为什么要问你呢?
Well, why is she asking you?
我不知道 她以为是我从阿奇博尔德那儿偷的
I don't know, she thought I stole it from Archibald,
我一直告诉她那东西被毁掉了 可她不相信我
and I kept telling her that it was destroyed, and she didn't believe me.
是被毁掉了 对吧?
It was destroyed, right?
是啊 当然
Yes, of course.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
我只是随便说说 要是你错了呢?
I'm just saying, what if you're wrong?
要是它还在外面
What if it's still out there
假冒者得到它并且打开入口呢?
and the shifter gets a hold of it and opens the portal?
钥匙已经不存在了
The key no longer exists.
我亲眼看见它被毁了
I saw it get destroyed.
没有人能打开那个入口了
No one's opening that portal ever again.
好吧 不过它的分支...
Okay, but the ramus mortium...
正在入口附近的地下墓穴里生长
It was growing in the catacombs near the entrance.
这不仅仅是巧合 对吗?
I think that's more than a coincidence, right?
没有钥匙没有人能打开那扇门
No one can open that door without the key.
钥匙已经不见了
The key is gone.
温迪 别再担心了
Wendy, stop worrying.
好吧 要担心的事还多着呢
Well, it's a lot to worry about.
什么?
What?
你的项链... 变红了
Your necklace... it's red.
这是你最后一条命了
This is your last life.
我需要更多的能量
I need more power.
有了
Yes.
谢天谢地...
Thank God...